protectionthroughgold.com 2018-09-19

# Protection Through Gold - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is **important** to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.   
To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our website (in the form of a link back to this page) at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can order products / online memberships, make requests, and register to receive further information. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:  
*Name  
*Email Address  
*Postal Address  
*Phone Number

Credit/Debit Card Information. Payment information including credit card information when entered for purchases, is only ever collected by the payment processors used by PTG (Paypal and Stripe - the 2 largest and most trusted online payment gateways) for the purpose of making membership payments and never captured and stored by PTG (Protection Through Gold).

We use the information you provide about yourself when requesting information only to complete that information request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the necessary information request. Your personal information (such as name and email) is only every shared with your direct referrer to PTG to better assist you with using the Sales Funnel system.  
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.  
You can register with our website if you would like to receive our blog updates as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.  
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.  
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by calling us or sending us an email.. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.  
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.  
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us by submitting a ticket at our Support Portal and one of our helpful Customer Success Team will assist you with your queries.
